Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series
Episode 115
Go away, Osman Bey!
You will stop.
If the blood that shed was yours...
would you stop?
I would definitely stop!
I would definitely stop.
If you move without
knowing the truth...
other people's blood will be shed.
Karesi Bey
I know.
I know your pain is great.
(I know you're sorry.)
I understand you well.
But you have to stop.
You took the person I
considered my son from me.
Please, Beys!
Stop, Beys!
In difficult times like these, unity
is necessary.
Karesi Bey.
You talk about the truth.
The truth!
I'll just stop until the truth comes out.
I will stop.
Alps!
Arrest Osman Bey's nephew.
You're making a
mistake, Karesi Bey.
While there are all these mistakes...
Let me make another one,
is that too much?
I will leave him alive.
I will control my anger.
I will not kill Aktemur, but I
will arrest him.
Don't ask me for
more than that, Osman Bey.
Karesi Bey.
I tell you that I vouch for my nephew
and you still insist on his arrest!
Don't fall for these games.
They do this in
order to spoil our unity.
Don't fall for these tricks.
I don't care about the unity.
It can be fixed anyway.
But my son-in-law...
My son-in-law cannot be
returned, Osman Bey.
Get out of my way.
No one will wield their sword until
an order comes from within, Alps.
If they don't fight us, we won't
fight them, Konur.
You draw swords where you are guests.
We draw them
until things clear up.
When things clear up, we'll
break them if needed.
Take him.
If you are Osman's nephew...
You will be jailed.
I hope it turns out that it is a game of
the enemy, as you said, Osman Bey.
Otherwise, if it turns out that
Aktemur is the guilty one...
there will be no
agreement or unity between us.
You should know that.
But if it turns out that you
are the one behind this...
Then no one will leave my land alive.
I'm not someone who would kill
your son-in-law...
And I'm not the one to plan
games behind your back.
I see your pain.
Because I see your pain...
I will ignore your threat.
These lands are definitely yours.
But learn this...
In these lands, it is not clear whose
head will be cut off.
Try, Osman Bey, try.
I am not a man who is afraid.
Who knows the truth
is never afraid of death.
But look...
I did not draw my
sword in your face.
Karesi Bey.
I will face those oppressors, you
and me together.
Then you will see...
I take you on my side.
I consider you one of us.
You will see the truth.
Then, you will ask me for forgiveness.
Beys.
What is happening here?
You tried to act without me again.
You smeared the place with blood.
Do you feel this, Orhan Bey?
I don't feel anything.
In the name of Allah.
Like a stone.
My body is like a stone, Kumral Abdal.
Don't be afraid, son.
You will recover.
I got up, mother.
My arm was fine.
But now...
Now, I can't feel any part of my body.
Mother.
Say something.
Will I never get up again?
No, my dear Orhan, you will heal.
You will stand up again.
We are here, dear Orhan.
Rest a little
Poison.
It won't kill him, but it makes
him weak.
What are you saying, Kumral Abdal?
Will Orhan not
get up again?
Do not say this, Kumral Abdal.
Is there no cure for this?
Can't you do anything?
I would raise armies.
I would complete my father's call.
With this helpless foot,
which state will I conquer?
With these arms...
On which oppressor will I draw my sword?
I'm dead,
I'm dead now.
You are not dead, my brother
You will live.
I will become your foot if your
foot does not move...
and I will become your
hand if your hand does not move.
But you will live.
Karesi Bey.
I have known Osman Bey for a long time.
He is a disobedient and stubborn person.
But he is not a Bey who does this
in a place where he is a guest.
He is not the one
who did this, Mother Sultan.
His nephew Aktemur...
argued with Uslu, my son-in-law...
- then, at night...
- He didn't do it.
I know the traitor who did this.
His intention is to divide
you and us with sedition.
This traitor who come between us...
is now with us.
Who is he, Mother Sultan?
While he...
is can't even be prey...
he tried to be a hunter.
Mother Sultan.
You dog!
What is your evidence?
Although the situation
exonerates you and your nephew...
why do you
ask for evidence, Osman Bey?
We are not looking for innocence,
we are looking for the truth
Tell me now.
What is the relationship between the blood
that was spilled in this palace and Avcı?
Osman Bey.
You are asking for evidence,
then I will prove it.
Celali.
If you want proof...
look at the dead.
Both contain the seal
of the Mongols.
You collaborate with
dogs and kill my nephew?
You will die like dogs.
You will remain calm, Karesi Bey.
The traitor betrayed me.
And justice is my justice.
He will die like a dog.
Do not worry.
Then he will be questioned.
If it takes to interrogate a dog
I've had all these years...
I will interrogate him.
Take him.
He died, my Sultan.
Nobody needs to worry.
There is justice in where I am.
Let this be the last thing
you don't depend on me, Karesi Bey.
Next time, I'll make you hurt.
Take your corpse.
Let's go now, we have important
matters to discuss.
Brothers.
What's going on
here, brother?
Brother, this isn't the time for questions
now, we're in a hurry.
You and Aykut will follow Avcı.
The place where the dead goes is
known, my brother, it is the cemetery.
Yes brother, just follow him, my Bey
clearly suspects something.
If there's something
behind this, we'll find it.
Come on, brother.
Come on, be careful.
Does Naiman have so much power that
he can kill my son-in-law in my palace?
He is so powerful that he
buys the helper...
who has been at Sultan Aladdin's
mother's side for years.
In short, the matter is
greater than the late Uslu Bey.
If we do not unite, and stand
up to the oppressor...
Thousands will die like him.
Isn't it, Osman Bey?
We are here for that.
Karesi Bey and I
have agreed...
And Candar Bey is behind us.
Yakup Bey, ruler of the Germiyanids, who
has the largest army in these lands...
stands behind me.
That is why you will stand behind me.
Karesi Bey.
Osman Bey.
It won't be easy for you both.
Osman Bey made a great effort
to convince me and Candar Bey.
He gave me his property.
- Instead of being satisfied...
- No...
We do nothing for ourselves.
While there is a calamity coming upon us...
we never care
who will have the leadership role.
As Yakup Bey, son
of Germiyanids...
who says that he can solve
problems with gold...
accepts the war...
Then, we will accept to
stand behind Mother Sultan.
Can I believe you?
Mother Sultan.
Naiman is coming to our lands with
about forty thousand Mongol soldiers.
None of the Bey
wanted to fight this war.
I called them to battle.
But now, I see
that the Beys agree to fight.
If our army is going to win this war, it
doesn't matter who will be in command.
You amaze us, Osman Bey.
Who will be surprised is Naiman,
as will be defeated in this war.
So, you are invited to the council of
war that I will hold in Yenişehir.
We will talk about the army that we will
establish and our war campaigns there.
Of course, we will be
there, Mother Sultan.
I am always ready
as long as we fight the enemy.
You are free now, Aktemur
Bey, as you deserve.
Thank you, Boran.
Justice always takes its course.
Yes.
How is Orhan Bey doing?
He is fine
and will get better, Inshallah.
Inshallah, did you find someone
who committed this betrayal?
We haven't found him yet, my daughter,
but we will.
No one will escape punishment.
If Orhan Bey does not recover, the chair
will belong to Aladdin Bey, right?
It's not the time to talk about this, Bengi
Hatun. Orhan will recover, Inshallah.
He will definitely get better, Inshallah.
There's something going on in my mind
but, I'm afraid you'll get me wrong.
If there is anything you know,
tell us, Bengi Hatun.
Orha Bey is the heir to rule
in the Kayı tribe, right?
I mean, he was like that before
he was bedridden.
I hope Aladdin Bey
hasn't done something stupid.
He is still young and reckless.
It is possible that he
is tempted by something.
How can you slander my son, Bengi Hatun?
Realize what you're saying, Hatun.
- Or are you...
- I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything, mother.
- Son.
- I didn't do anything.
Son.
Aladdin.
My son.
Mother Sultan.
Nobody knows that Avcı is
alive, right, Celali?
Yes, Mother Sultan.
No one doubted.
And we got out of town undercover.
From now on, you're a dead man, Avcı.
You will not appear on the
scene without my order.
While it would have been easy
to kill me, why didn't you?
I don't sacrifice my garbage for the sake
of Osman, how will I sacrifice one of my men?
People thinking you are a dead man will
facilitate my future campaigns.
You will go to Olof, and you will
hide in İnegöl.
My success in getting the Beys
behind me tied Osman's hands.
Now we will tie Olof's hands.
When the time comes...
We'll throw Olof into the
flames to clear our way.
My Bey was right.
Mother Sultan manipulates everyone.
Let's tell Osman Bey immediately, brother,
come on.
Frigg did this
and we'll catch her sooner or later.
We have to get her
out of İnegöl first, Malhun.
- Mother.
- Yes.
Can't you do something?
We couldn't crush Olof's head, let's
at least help them with Frigg problem.
What am I going to do, my daughter?
I haven't seen that snake
since the truth came out.
Besides, how
can I get her out of the castle?
İnegöl Castle.
I've sent word to our brothers in the
north, we'll be more powerful now.
With or without them, my love.
I will soon have the lands I promised you.
This will never be easy.
As long as Jesus' chosen soldiers are with
me, no one can stand against us.
There is no one braver
than Odin's warriors, Olof.
I fear you will realize
this on the battlefield.
There is no fear in the hearts of those
who fight for Jesus, Frigg.
You will know this when you feel the
greatness of Christianity in your heart.
- Olof.
- Frigg.
Tell me what did you learn.
Osman has gone
to the lands of Karasids, Olof.
There is no trace of Turgut either.
Osman's lands have never
been so unprotected.
They are waiting for us to lead
them like an obedient lamb.
Let's make war, Olof.
What are we waiting for?
Let's turn Osman's lands into a lake
of blood in his absence.
If Osman doesn't attack us even though
İnegöl is under our control...
He must be planning a campaign.
So, what do we do?
We will attack everywhere.
We'll take everything that Osman has
without allowing him to make any campaign.
Make preparations.
We will go to take back
the lands that belong to us.
Olof.
Where are you going?
To the church, I will pray to God.
- Tell me, Alps.
- We followed Avcı, as you commanded, my Bey.
He's not dead, Mother Sultan plans a game.
What are you saying?
İsmihan.
I wanted to believe you
because times are hard.
But no, no.
People of sedition always
think of their interests.
I will strangle you with your tricks.
How did you understand, my Bey?
I doubted her helping us.
I was right in my suspicions.
What shall we do now, my Bey?
You will go with Turgut Bey.
But you will catch him alive.
Don't let him run away.
- The truth will come out sooner or later.
- Your command, my Bey.
Let's go.
Collect all the weapons from the surrounding
villages and bring them to the castle.
May the great Jesus protect you.
Cerkutay.
Those will do a very bad job.
They will attack somewhere but...
We'll know, Ülgen Hatun.
Come.
Your present task
is difficult, Ülgen Hatun.
What are you saying? You
won't leave me alone, will you?
What? Are you scared?
You were saying: "I don't want Cerkutay
and I'll work it out on my own."
Yes, I said that so you
wouldn't be afraid.
I'm Kara's daughter,
why should I be afraid?
You would be afraid in the
country of strangers...
when you're separated from me.
You...
are Kara's daughter.
You have a soft heart.
You are virtuous and brave...
Ülgen Hatun.
Now...
Go to Olof's church and find out
where they are preparing to attack.
Be careful.
And you, what will you do?
I'll go to the armory and smash it.
Those dogs will
lose their passion.
Alone? Do you want to die, Cerkutay?
I will come with you too.
If we are worrying about our life, what
are we doing here, Ülgen Hatun?
But you stay.
Stay alive.
Okay, then.
You shall go in peace, and you
shall return in peace, Cerkutay.
Cerkutay does not die.
- Give me a promise.
- I promise.
Good.
I'm going make Olof talk.
There's no getting away from this
I will make him tweet like a nightingale.
Is it possible that you
wouldn't do that, Ülgen Hatun?
- Cerkutay?
- Yes.
Be careful, okay?
I haven't learned how to draw a sword
well yet.
You'll teach me that, don't forget.
I will never forget.
Let's go.
May it be a cure for my son.
Son.
Aladdin.
My brother?
If my brother can't get out of that bed...
If he dies because of my sword...
Aladdin.
Then my blood will be lawful for
you, my mother, Malhun.
Kill me with this sword.
I never ever hear that from you again!
Nothing will happen
to you or your brother.
I will never allow this.
We will not allow it.
We will make those, who made us live
through this, pay for this.
May Allah help us.
This place is good, light a fire, Torahan.
Your command, my Bey.
What shall we do now, my Bey?
We'll spend the night here.
We'll get to the council tomorrow.
Let's see Avcı first.
When Avcı comes, we'll understand what
Mother Sultan is up to.
Then, rest is the war.
Let's send word to the tribe, then let the
preparations begin.
The coming of Naiman is not a secret,
Orhan will be at the head of the Alps.
They must have made all the preparations.
Take this.
In the name of Allah.
Let's see.
My Bey.
Thank you.
They broke your branch, Osman.
Where are you?
Bear a little, my son,
bear, my hero.
My Allah.
I lost my mother at an early age.
I buried my brothers and
my father with my own hands.
My heart is tired of
all those pains, but...
this is much more difficult, My Allah.
I pretend to be patient.
I pretend to be patient...
but my strength is not enough, my Allah.
I'm so desperate.
My Allah.
Please, my Allah.
Test me with my life, but don't test
me with my son's life, my Allah.
You are the haven of the desperate.
You are generous and you are kind.
We have no refuge but You.
You are the cure for this disease.
Please, my Allah.
Please, grant him health.
Heal him.
I have no one but my sons.
Please, save them for me, my Allah.
Please, my Allah, save Orhan for me.
Amin.
Amin, my Allah.
Osman.
Where are you?
Orhan.
My Bey.
Are you okay, my Bey?
Near Yenişehir
Caravansary
Whatever Osman wished for, he
did not succeed in it.
First, he wanted to gather
the Beys behind him but...
When he did not succeed, he
was forced to obey.
Osman is loyal to us now, Bayındır.
A game is always being hatched in his head.
Let's see what appears before us.
Whatever, Mother Sultan.
Osman will always be
disappointed in front of you.
Getting rid of the scourge of Osman
and Naiman as well.
This is our first goal, Bayındır.
We kill two birds with one stone.
You will not hesitate to make
any sacrifice for that.
As you wish, Mother Sultan.
My neck is sacrificed
for your sake, if you wish.
Keep your neck to yourself, Bayındır.
Your sincerity is enough.
Beys will come in the morning.
Receive them in the best way.
So that we can handle Naiman when
he attacks us.
İnegöl Castle
May the great Jesus
Christ accept your prayers...
Commander Olof.
Thank you, sister...
Irene.
Tell me.
Did that woman become a Christian?
First, repent.
You must make a confession.
If you do not confess, your
prayers will not be accepted.
Don't Catholics confess?
We are Orthodox..
Of course, of course it is.
I mean.. we...
what I wanted to say...
If there is...--
Whatever! Everyone is human!
You don't look like any nun I've known.
But I loved your ease.
Make a confession and the Great Jesus
will help you.
My first sin...
and my biggest sin...
when I was a kid...
Whatever, childhood is over!
What about sooner...
For example, yesterday...
Yesterday?
Perhaps, it'd be best for me to speak to
your brother, Reverend Simon.
Possible, talk to Simon.
I...--
will call Simon and come here.
Why are you afraid, Ülgen?
You almost messed it up.
I'll tell you the names of
the villages you will attack.
Now, hear me carefully.
Yenişehir
Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome, Yakup Bey.
- Welcome, Yakup Bey.
- You're welcomed!
Welcome, my Bey.
So, this is Yenişehir.
You think you are our equal
in this little town, Osman Bey.
Welcome, Karesi Bey.
Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome, my Bey, welcome.
My Bey, you are welcomed.
Welcome, my Bey.
You underestimated Söğüt
and took Yenişehir.
But, despite that, you could not
become like us, Osman Bey.
Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome, my Bey, here you go.
Welcome, welcome, Candar Bey.
Welcome, my Bey.
Come, please.
You pulled us to your side
and then backed away.
So, the right thing is to be behind Mother Sultan.
Welcome!
I thought you were smart.
What do you say, Yakup Bey?
The great Candar.
Does a person obey
someone who's younger than him?
Will you stand behind Osman Bey?
What about you, Karesi Bey?
You, who are going to become
the ruler of the seas,
what convinced you to stand behind...
a shepherd?
We certainly have reasonable reasons.
I beg your pardon, Mother Sultan.
Say it.
What makes you stand behind Mother Sultan?
Loyalty.
Loyalty to my country.
If we're going to fight, we are fighting
for the Seljuk state.
If a council of war is to be held...
Seljuk state holds it.
Let's say Mother Sultan backed down.
When I'm here...
Does Osman Bey have the
right to become a leader?
Osman Bey is not an enemy.
But...
Who has strength?
Who has army?
You made a mistake, so, shut
up politely.
It is clear that the war promise
you made to Osman...
made Yakup Bey very angry.
Don't worry.
I don't accuse you of treason, nor
do I get angry with you.
Thank you all.
You answered my invitation.
Yakup Bey.
In difficult times like this, anger is
only towards the enemy.
Let it be as you said, Mother Sultan.
In fact, I love Candar Bey and
Karesi Bey like my two little brothers.
Yakup Bey.
You should love your
little brother first.
Perhaps this is what prompted us to
stand behind Osman Bey.
You have to get rid of your arrogance.
Beys.
Calm down.
We came here to talk about our campaign...
not to argue.
Here.
It's the end of the road for you, Avcı.
What are you going to do?
Now, when I kill you...
you will understand
whose end has come.
Come on, Alps.
Mother Sultan will hold
you accountable for this.
You will not be able to escape from
her hands this time, Turgut.
When I will get the truth
from that poisonous tongue of yours...
Mother sultan will not
be able to do anything.
Tell me everything.
Why did Mother Sultan do such a thing?
Why did she keep you alive?
Speak!
It's not my time yet.
To gather Beys behind her!
And what
about İnegöl?
Why did you sell my İnegöl
to Olof?
Speak!
We didn't sell it!
You are lying.
Avcı, you are lying to me!
We didn't sell it.
Olof took it.
And what about Yenişehir?
Are you the ones who
made people there sick?
poisoned innocent people?
What's the reason?
Leave me, if I tell you this, Mother
Sultan will kill me.
Avcı.
Did you think we'd let you live?
Turgut Bey.
He won't talk.
Let the tongue cease,
and the sword speaks!
No, no, he won't die like that, Aykut.
Bring the horses.
So that we could tie each of his organ
to a horse.
He can go to Karesi.
He can go to Candar.
He can go to Germiyanids.
May Avcı, the faithful servant of Mother
Sultan, go all around the world.
Avcı.
You are a hero who loves his country
so much that I...
I will scatter your pieces
all around the country.
So that people will learn from you.
They should know you.
Come on, where are the horses?
Stop!
We did it.
Frigg did it
behest of Mother Sultan.
No, not enough.
You will tell us everything.
Now tell me.
That matter in the Karesi tribe council...
Why did it fall on you?
Because the one who found the traitor
and guaranteed justice is Mother Sultan.
She lined everyone up behind her...
and ended the reputation of Osman Bey.
Avcı.
- That's enough!
- Stop, I'll say everything!
No.
You won't tell me anything now.
If you will, you will
tell everything in front of the council.
So that everyone knows the truth.
You will rest then.
Take this dog.
Let's go.
My Bey.
I got news.
Naiman will...
seem to enter Candar Bey
and Karesi Bey's lands...
and make us disperse our army.
But his main goal is...
to head for these lands.
What if he actually
does what he says?
I do not have a unit
in my home country.
Because I am here with you.
Calm down, Candar Bey.
If we weren't sure...
we'd have sent the five thousand horsemen
of Yakup Bey to your country.
However, Naiman...
will come here.
Are we sure...
we have the power to
end Naiman, Mother Sultan?
The Germiyan cavalry
often defeated the Mongols.
Don't you trust your Alps?
We trust them, Yakup Bey,
we trust them.
The possibility
made us feel bad.
When Naiman reaches these lands...
Yakup Bey and I will meet him.
Candar Bey.
Karesi Bey.
You will weaken him
from the left and right fronts.
Where is Osman Bey?
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Here I come.
I have come to tell you that
your campaigns (move) are wrong.
And what is the correct one?
Enlighten us with
your right thoughts...
Osman Bey.
I will enlighten you,
or we shall all be defeated together.
My Bey!
Avcı!
They are there.
Let's chase them.
Baysungur, Acar.
You two stay with Avcı.
Kutan, Aykut,
you two cut out their way.
Don't, Avcı, don't.
Don't die.
İsmihan never stops messing with us.
She thought of all our moves.
What shall we do now, my Bey?
Now...
Avcı has to live.
Come on, valiants.
Let's go.
He has to live.
Avcı must live.
In the name of Allah.
Tell me, how's he?
My Bey, it doesn't look like
he's going to survive.
He will die.
His death is not a good thing.
The truth will not appear
like that.
Many innocent people will die.
May Allah help us.
Your words are very challenging.
What's that you know...
and we don't?
You are heading towards the ambush.
We are aware of this ambush.
You just think you
are aware of the ambush.
However...
This is the ambush itself.
Don't underestimate, Naiman.
He misleads your intelligence.
He has spies among you.
He is dragging you into a trap.
Speak...
Osman Bey.
Yakup Bey.
Have you sent Alps to
the lands of Candar Bey?
I haven't.
Here I am with my 20,000 horsemen.
You think that Naiman
will go towards you with his whole army.
We don't think, Osman Bey,
but we know that.
Candar Bey.
I told you that he has spies among you.
Knowing that you are
gathered here, he changed his plan.
First...
The Mongol soldiers started entering
your lands from the northern side.
The other part of the soldiers...
began to enter Karesi Bey's territory.
If you want to defeat the enemy...
you should think like him.
He knows that Yakup Bey's entire
army is here.
And what about you?
There is no trick in your plans.
Here is your army
standing here, straight as a wall.
I see that you underestimate the enemy.
Do you think you're smarter than
everyone here right now?
No, I think Naiman's move
is better than yours.
He will not come here
with his entire army.
Enough, Osman Bey.
There is no such thing as "we."
You are not part of
this army anymore.
And you have no right to speak either!
What do you know about us
to talk about spies?
No rotten fruit grows on our tree.
Naiman is coming here with his whole army.
We will wait for
him here together.
Yakup Bey, you'll give five thousand
of your horsemen to Candar Bey.
You'll give another five thousand
of your horsemen to Karesi Bey.
Otherwise, they will destroy us.
What if he's
telling the truth?
Osman Bey is not telling the truth.
He would like us to be
defeated and lose our reputation.
He wants to do what the enemy wanted and
couldn't achieve. He wants our break up.
There is no place for
his ideas in this council.
If you don't do what I said...
They will turn our country, which
looks like heaven, into hell.
You are not part
of this army anymore.
Your words won't apply to the army, which
you're not a part of, Osman Bey.
You will burn these lands because of your stubbornness
It's not about stubbornness, Osman Bey.
We are sure about our plan.
You will see, we will win.
This move won't bring us victory.
It'll be our end.
When the lands of
Candar and Karasi burn
They will have surrounded us
from the north and the south
They will have surrounded our armies
Mother Sultan.
If we do this, our defeat becomes certain.
Osman Bey, it's enough.
Go to your tribe if you don't want
to held in prison during the war.
Don't bother us anymore.
You are too arrogant to hear my words.
Naiman will build a tower out of your heads.
Remember what I just said.
And this is my last word.
Osman Bey.
Is it bad news?
My Bey, it's Orhan Bey.
What happened to Orhan?
Orhan Bey is poisoned, my Bey.
What are you saying?
Is he okay?
He is fine.
But he can't get out of bed,
he can't move any part of his body
Orhan...
Thank you.
Alps!
The work is not finished, it is not finished!
There is a lot of work.
- Is there anything else left?
- There are few left.
Help me to finish it
Ignobles!
Let me introduce you to Cerkutay.
- What is happening here?
- What is this rumble about?
Who is there inside?
I'm coming! Wait!
Wait, wait a little more.
Open the door, what's going on inside?
Come on, open this door!
I'll open, wait, wait, wait!
I will open, I will open all the doors now.
Coming, coming.
Open the door, who are you?
Answer!
Hang on!
Or don't, up to you.
Traitor!
Let the state be above your cradle
For sugar and syrup
Sleep baby, sleep
My son, whom I raised with lullabies
What a great exam is this?
But you will also pass this exam.
You are very strong.
You will stand back on your feet.
Osman.
Orhan.
Osman, Osman
they poisoned our son.
They broke my arms and wings
Malhun.
No, no, don't cry.
Dear Malhun,
I can't stand the tears in your eyes
Don't cry, don't cry
No, our arms and wings must heal.
Our son will recover.
He must be fine, he must be fine.
He will heal, right?
He will heal
He will heal, he will heal
He will heal, Malhun
You will stand strong like this
Thank Allah
he has a mother like you behind him
You stand behind him like a mountain
Malhun, you have to be strong.
You have to be strong in order to
help him.
He has his mother standing behind him
like a mountain
Keep your heart at ease, keep it at ease.
He will be fine.
He'll be fine, he'll be fine.
Can I, my Bey.
Come in, Kumral Abdal.
Come.
Orhan, Orhan, son
Kumral Abdal, how is his condition?
I can't identify the poison, my Bey.
It does not kill, but it keeps him powerless
How?
He cannot move any part of his body.
What kind of poison is this?
We don't know, my Bey.
It's a poison unlike anything I know
It affects the body slowly.
Marmaragic Castle
Alcicek
Get the other packs, come on
You stop.
Do not you dare
Don't say a single word
about poison, Esma.
If not today, they will understand
that I did it someday.
What will we do then?
They will not realise.
You will shut up
and they will search for the traitor
But both Aladdin Bey and Orhan Bey
saw me in the tent.
If not today, then tomorrow!
They see you in the tent every day!
You go into that tent every day!
They won't suspect you.
But if, let's say, you made
a mistake and they realised you...
Then you won't say my name.
Reveal Ismihan or Avci, whomever
you want!
Think of your sister.
You have brought this
misfortune upon us, Bengi Hatun.
What are you saying, Esma?
Mother!
How could you do this?
You will gather everyone around us!
Let them!
What did you do?
Why did you commit this betrayal?
Esma!
Say something, Esma!
I was forced!
They forced me for my sister 's sake,
Alcicek Hatun!
Esma!
This is the hardest part of motherhood.
My son is in pain
As for me, my heart becomes hell.
A wolf gives birth to wolves solely.
As long as he has a mother like you...
...don't worry, he
will get over this.
He'll get over this.
But those who broke my branch...
...those who did this to my son...
I will rip their hearts out with my own hands.
We'll both do it!
Orhan
Father.
Orhan.
No no.
No, Orhan
Orhan.
Mother.
Son.
Straighten me up.
Okay son
Dear Orhan.
Son.
- Father.
- Yes.
I don't want you
to see me crippled like that.
Son!
How can you speak like that!?
Never again you shall speak of it.
You will recover.
You will recover if Allah permits.
Kumral Abdal.
He did everything he could
but still nothing, father.
I...
I became a burden to you.
Can a son become a burden on his parents?
I carried you in my womb for nine months.
I will carry you on my back
for the rest of my life.
I just want you to be fine, son.
Just be fine.
Not possible like this, mother.
Is this how a son of
a Bey should be like?
I can't even raise my arms.
I am a burden to you.
A burden to my father.
Especially to my brother.
I am in pain of remorse.
Look at me.
You are not a burden to me.
Neither to you tribe.
Son.
You are my secret.
You are my first child.
Don't.
You won't give up, son.
The day you moved your finger...
...I understood you were strong.
You are strong, you will never give up.
You will be fine.
And you will hold them
accountable for doing this to you
We will hold them accountable.
We will hold them all accountable,
back to back.
You will rise to your feet against the enemy
Look at me.
You will never give up.
Promise me.
You will get out of this bed
no matter what.
I promise you, father.
I promise I will get up.
Inegol Castle
Oh my!
Cerkutay!
What if they do something to him?
What if they caught him?
He would have already come otherwise...
...Priest HÄ±risto!
Do not worry.
Cerkutay knows Inegol
better than Olof and his men
And the castle too.
He will come without being caught.
Yes he knows, right?
He knows everything.
He is skilled in sword fighting.
Oh Allah, may he return safely, and I will cook
for him burghur with meat!
I heard you!
You said you'd cook bulghur with meat!
You must keep your word, Ulgen Hatun.
Cerkutay!
You're here!
But... what happened to you?
Do not worry.
It was a piece of cake for me.
I blew up their weapons store.
And also a couple...
Seven...
No more than seven...
I killed many of their soldiers.
Praise be!
But...
When I got out the main event started.
Many soldiers started to surround me.
If I did not know about
the secret tunnel...
...I would be in real trouble.
Allah forbid!
I couldn't reach martyrdom again.
But...
I will teach you how to use a sword.
It's not easy,
is it, Ulgen Hatun?
Yes, you will teach me, if Allah permits.
It's not easy!
What did you do meanwhile?
Is there any news?
Why did Olof make all that preparation for?
I couldn't learn anything
from that obnoxious Olof!
But I heard from his soldiers.
You know, they'll attack Muslim towns
near Inegol...
I heard all of the names of the towns.
I memorised.
Great.
We must inform our Bey.
They have no weapon to fight though.
However, we must still be careful.
We will be after them.
Someone comes...
And blows up my weapon storage...
And you don't know anything!
Who did this?
How did you not see him?!
Is not my life and
my castle entrusted to you?
You will find him/her, do you understand?
You will investigate all the strangers you see!
Olof!
Do you understand?!
I am sure Osman is involved in this!
You will find him/her!
If you don't find him/her...
...I will kill you all!
There is news, Olof.
A caravan.
A Turkish caravan set out on its way
to the Byzantine state.
It is loaded with a lot of goods.
They will pass by the path
near Inegol in the morning.
My Cicek(flower)
- My beautiful daughter...
- Do not you dare!
Don't ever call me daughter
without telling me about it!
How could you do such evil?
You will tell me.
Notice your limits!
No.
Not this time.
You don't get to hit me this time.
You are the guilty one now.
I did not do anything.
Rather, the snake, Ismihan did it.
She used my name!
Tell me from the beginning.
From the beginning.
Did you make Esma a spy?
Yes, I made her!
In order to get news from the palace.
That's it.
I had no other intention.
You threatened her with her sister!
Were you going to kill the child whom
you raised, too after beacuse she had no family?!
Have you always been this evil, Mother?
You speak big words, Alcicek.
I did not differentiate between
you and those two girls!
I frightened Esma to make her
do her job secretly and decently.
But things got complicated!
If Ismihan did it, why are we guilty?
Ismihan stained Esma's hand with blood.
Esma is from out tribe.
If they learn about Esma...
Before Ismihan, we'll be in trouble!
Not just me.
Your father and you will
be in trouble too.
Then you will not be able to marry Aktemur,
whom you have loved so much throughout your life
Then you're going to help them catch that snake
called Frigg, Mother!
You will find the antidote
and make Orhan recover!
Otherwise, aside from Aktemur...
I will sacrifice my life and
tell everything to Osman Bey myself!
Avci's death was not good at all, my Bey.
So we'll make another plan.
They pushed us out from the war.
They banished us from the army.
But we will take precautions.
We will form a defense line.
And no one will cross this line.
We will not allow them, of course!
Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too
I hope the best for you.
Do not worry.
Orhan is strong.
We fought a lot back to back.
I know his strength is greater than his age.
Whatever the calamity that put
him into this situation...
With the strength of his family, he will
surely push this it away.
Of course.
He will be stronger than ever.
Inshallah.
But...
His exam is difficult right now.
Our exam doesn't seem very easy either.
We've never experienced
anything more difficult.
Right now...
They think that Naiman's army
will attack them in one body.
They don't realise that...
They will be attaced from
divided troops.
From north to Candar,
From south to Karasi.
Their spies think this is a trap.
We will not establish our defence
line in the east
We will defend the north and the south.
For this reason, Send news to Sahin Bey,
Demirhan Bey and Uraz Bey.
They'll give us a thousand cavalry.
They will wait in the North.
And they will destroy those
who come from there in this valley
But they should know that...
...no alp will die before
killing 10 Mongol soldiers!
I'm blocking the path of the ignobles
coming from the south.
You will not come with us.
Why?
We always talk about the enemy in the east.
What about those in the West?
You will attack Olof.
I gave up my castle, Ingol Castle,
for the war against the Naiman.
Why would Olof be a problem for me?
He is a problem of course.
He's waiting for us to stumble.
At that time, he'll want to
conquer these castles.
He will want to attack the tribes
when he hears of the departure of the Beys.
If we do not protect our back,
we can't establish a line of defense here
As you say...
I will pounce on his head the
moment he takes his head out of that castle.
We will watch our back too.
Malhun Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
You two will organize The Sisters
You two will find who did this to my Orhan!
If we can't find...
...who did this...
...breathing is forbidden to us.
The enemy is also walking towards us,
let them come.
It won't be over until
we announce it's over.
What if Osman Bey is right?
I have never witnessed that
although I have been here for a while.
Osman wants to be the sole ruler.
We will lose if we believe him.
What will Osman gain if we lose?
He will gain dominance.
Osman wanted to be at the
head of the army, but he did not succeed.
He wants to drive us to defeat now.
Othman will be stronger
if we lose our strength.
Candar Bey and Karasi Bey
showed interest in him.
His influence on nomads is also great.
That's why we don't have a
chance to make a mistake.
We will win this war.
We will level Osman's reputation
to the ground.
So that the nomads will go
to your lands and not to his lands.
Let us get rid of this trouble first.
What if Osman tries to make a move
and makes the situation even more difficult?
I can't stand
Osman anymore, Yakup Bey.
I will jail him if he confronts me again.
Mother Sultan, is it a good idea
to go that far in this troubled times?
Everyone goes far in relieved times.
You are with me because I go far
in difficult times, Yaup Bey.
We will destroy Naiman and
weaken Osman's power
We will come out of this
difficult time stronger.
O my Creator.
What kind of pain is this?
What kind of fire is this, my Creator?
My son's pain...
It cauterizes my heart
O Creator.
But his grief...
His grief is not for himself.
He says:
"I was going to be a Bey...
...but I ended up being a burden."
He says he has become a burden.
O Creator, O Creator,
he feels bad for us.
Oh my Allah, you
are generous, my Creator!
Grant us the strength of
patience in this exam.
You are the healer,
the cure comes from you, my Creator!
You heal whomever you want.
Oh my Allah, grant healing to all
those who seek healing, to my son, to Orhan.
Heal him, my Creator.
The disease comes from you just like
the cure comes from you, my Creator.
Heal him, my Creator.
Grant us with your mercy.
Amen.
My sheikh, my sheikh.
I feel ashamed to be healthy.
Being able to move my arms and legs in
front of my son hurts me.
It hurts me, it hurts me my sheih.
When I see my son like that...
"I would like to follow the path of Hadrat Abraham"
"I would like to break the idols"
.Didn't you say these, Osman Bey?
Did you not know that you would be tested
with such tests in this path that you were asking for?
No.
Not breaking idols.
The knife that is on my son's neck...
I witnessed that.
I now understand it's
extreemly difficult to be Abraham.
I understand now.
I didn't know, my sheikh.
Seeing my son
so helpless, so sad...
He says he has become a burden,
he says he has become a shame
But not for himself.
Because he cannot serve the cauase.
This, my sheikh, is difficult to bear.
This weighs on me, this weighs on me.
Osman Bey, had it not been for these
difficulties and these exams
...how would we get closer to our Cretor?
Think, he gives his hardest
exams to the people he loves the most.
To his messengers.
We shall know that all this is happening
for a cause...
And that way we complete
the exam successfully.
We will put our hands over our hearts
in all circumstances and say, Alhamdulillah
Alhmdulillah. (Than Allah)
We need to realise that our Creator
is the true owner of his blessings...
...including children.
We need to, yes.
You feel pain now because of the love
and compassion you feel for your children
But know that.
The mercy and love we have...
...is not even one percent of
Allah's love and mercy towards us.
If He has given us this
test, we have to be patient and trust
And we pray.
My Creator, who made your words
heal my heart shall also heal my son.
Inshallah.
Inshallah, my sheikh.
Inegol Castle.
You, the carriers of the wrath of north.
You will pour out your anger on that caravan.
No one will come out alive from
the caravan that we will target
The traitors who entered among us
have erased our weapons.
But our axes, our shields, and the fire
of our vengeance are with us!
- Long live Olof!
- Long live Olof, long live Olof!
With an axe, sword, chest, or bare hand!
We will shed blood today,
we will shed Turkish blood!
Jesus Christ is with us!
Cerkutay and Ulgen are in Inegol.
We can get Frigg
out of the castle with their help.
This is our last chance.
Let's send an informant quickly.
Can I?
Come, Bengi Hatun!
I will help you.
I sent a message to Frig
I told her that Mother Sultan had business with her,
and invited her to Marmaraci.
What's it, Bengi Hatun?
Why are you doing this favour to us?
We're related now, Malhun Hatun.
Apart from that, it's a matter of life
of a child.
When will I help
if I don't help on a day like this?!
So, we'll set an ambush
on the road and catch her.
Sent by Bengi Hatun.
Send my greetings.
What are you asking for again, Bengi?
Get my horse ready!
We're going to Marmaragic
We'll have a lot of
losses when it's all over.
But I will have won anyway.
I will be a hero who
even risked her life for her people.
The Sultan, the mother of the Attic Seljuk state,
and the guardian and protector of all Turkmens.
May Allah keep you on our head
Thank you, Bayindir.
You too will double your wealth
when this war is over.
Thanks to you, Hadrat Mother Sultan.
And you too, Oktem Bey,
will be rewarded for choosing the right side.
Thank you, Mother Sultan.
The army must be organized first.
You will also make
the necessary expenses for this, Bayindir.
Bayindir's wealth is t your service,
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
Don't worry.
All the Beys will contribute.
This is a huge war, Bayindir.
So big that you can't even imagine.
Are you saying that three
large emirates and dozens of armies...
...won't be enough, Mother Sultan?
Let's see the armies first.
Oktem Bey, you seem worried.
It's about Bey's.
No one is coming, Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan, Karasi Bey and his
army is approaching.
They can't disobey me
like they disobey Osman Bey.
Of course, Mother Sultan.
Of course they will come, Oktem Bey.
Father.
I will tell you something
But don't get angry
Son.
I'll be angry if I need to be.
Allah knows what I feel.
I'll let you know too, father.
I think about this all the
time, after what I did to my brother.
I... I
know you've waited so long for me.
- And you said that my birth was a miracle
- Yes.
I am not a miracle, father,
but I am a test for you
I caused my brother
to be in this situation
Maybe if I wasn't...
Son, how can you speak like that?
Tell me, does it suit you?
It was not appropriate for me to make my brother
fall in this position either, father.
But I caused it.
Raise your head
raise your head, Aladdin.
You are not the one who caused this.
Whoever did this wanted
to use you.
The ones who wanted to hurt him
could hurt him in other ways too.
Their intention was to use you.
Their goal is to create a
enmity between you brothers
Be careful.
Beware!
Don't fall into their plan.
Your brother will rise to his feet
just like how he fell.
And you, too, should not despair.
We will get through this together.
We'll rise together, son.
Come on son.
Come on let's see.
Bring that.
Give it to me.
Hold it.
We will always work; So
we can stand on our feet.
We must not stop
Let's go.
Let's go
O Allah! O Allah!
Brother, investigate what happened there.
Kill everyone.
Leave no one alive
Raise your shields
Olof
You shouldn't have gone outside those walls!
How fortunate I am
because I will take your soul now
The only thing I will give you
is my bloody sword, Turgut!
Come and take it!
At my command, alps.
Attack!
They are coming, Bala Hatun.
Come on, sisters,
our fight shall be blessed.
Let's go.
Come and see
you two-faced demon!
Come on sisters
O Right!
Oh Right!
Allah is the greatest!
I'm here Bala.
- I'm here.
- You Snake.
The Kayi Sisters will
ambush you on the way.
They asked me to summon you to
Marmaragic Castle, so be careful.
Today is the day of reckoning, Frigg.
You will pay for what you did.
Bala,
look around you.
Game is over.
Osman will not save you now.
And who will save you from my hands?
You will die today, Bala.
The end of these paths
leads to us, Frigg.
- Now!
- Oh Right!
Now is the time for you to pay for the
innocent blood you have shed, Olof!
I will not die without cutting off your heads
on these lands, Turgut!
Your soldiers are falling one by one.
Now I will rip your head off with my sword.
Yes, come, Turgut.
It's time for you to die by my sword.
Do you think I didn't get prepared?
Whatever you did...
...won't stop you from dying by my sword.
Do you think we don't know
about your plans?
Look at there.
Did you trust these, Olof?
Death is what cruels deserve!
Your end is to be hunted down!
Allah is mighty!
Allah is the greatest!
Olof!
Olof, we can't take it.
We must withdraw, Olof, come on!
No.
Come on Olof, your wound is deep!
Let's go!
No.
No!
Olof!
The sky might fell and the earth
might split open.
But there is no place
for you to hide.
I will be behind you like
the shadow of death.
You will not find rest in that
castle of yours!
Attack!
Game is over, Frigg.
Your life is in my hands.
Take this ignoble to the tribe!
How is going on with
the preparations?
Everyone is exercising
to ride horse.
Everyone will be able to fight,
Mother Sultan.
Preparations are going on.
Great.
Candar Bey.
Do you think of your homeland?
What else can a man think of, Mother Sultan?
Don't worry, your home is safe.
We'll beat that Nayman.
- Celale.
- Mother Sultan.
- There's a cavalry approaching.
- A cavalry?
I am the power of God!
Who are you?
I am a descendant of Genghis
and I will be the end of yours.
Nayman.
I've come from a
very long, long way
It's tasteless.
Just like your lands.
You claim that you will shed your blood
for the sake of these lands!
Ridiculous!
No
Let your leader come.
I am already here.
Shut up, woman.
I am talking about Osman.
No, Kumral Abdal, no.
I do not feel
Come on, come on
Let's go
Come on, one more time
Come on, come on, valiant.
Your biggest weakness...
...is that you are not choosing
your leader correctly
Mighty Genghis overcame many problems.
He was beaten and insulted.
So he became the leader.
What did Osman tell you?
He told you,
"Neman will deploy his armies, don't stand here."
What did you do?
You didn't care.
What I like most are
foolish enemies.
Easy booty
and lots of blood!
Osman was right.
A little bit of my army is here.
Because even
this is too much for you!
My armies sieged Candar's land.
The lands of Qarasi
is currently under siege.
Yakup Bey!
While your whole army is here,
Germiyan is a piece of cake for me.
How many soldiers are here?
Let's go out to the field.
My victory will not take long.
Because you became domasticated
in mansions and palaces.
But I am a hungry steppe wolf!
Do you think we're afraid, Nayman?
You are shaking, Mother Sultan.
I forgave your son Aladdin
for my interests.
But there is no reason
for me to let you live.
One hundred and fifty chests of gold
Your taxes will triple!
And you will give me
ten thousand horses.
You will dissolve your army here,
which is of no use
Hold on, son.
That's enough, I don't want to!
I can't move neither
my hands nor my feet!
I am dead!
This bed is my grave!
I can't hold the sword anymore!
You will, son!
You will hold the sword and
stand on your feet!
Do not give up!
What are you talking about, father?
Where are we going?
Osman.
- His treatment continues, my Bey.
- Osman, where are you taking Orhan?
Where are we going, father?
Lying time is over!
We'll get out of the tent first!
Father, don't do it, father!
I don't want them to see me like this.
No, son!
Being a Bey doesn't only require
being present on battlefields.
You will not be locked in the dark.
You will go out and see the light of day.
But we'll go to the training first!
You will leave neither
your sword nor your people.
But first
Son.
Come.
You will not give up.
Giving up is forbidden to us.
Now that you...
Now that you can't stand
up straight.
So we'll find another way.
If you have hope...
Son...
Then you will somehow stand up.
You'll get up somehow, son.
- Okay, Orhan?
- Okay, father.
Praise be to my valiant!
My son Orhan
He can't walk right now.
Like the situation in our country
The oppressors have been
oppressing us for a long time!
But no, we will not wait and
we will not be defeated!
It's timeto rise up for both Orhan and
for our country!
- Allah is the greatest!
My son Orhan, you will rise,
then our country will rise.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com